mipony.net 2012-12-30

# Mipony - Sugerencias

| 

Privacy policy of this web site

**Privacy Policy**

Through our privacy policy we inform you about politics of safe usage data and how we protect the privacy of the visitors.

The use of this web site, implies full and unreserved acceptance of all of the provisions contained in this Legal Notice, so if you do not agree with any of the terms established herein shall not use and / or access this site.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time. Your continued use of any portion of this site following notification or posting of such modifications will constitute your acceptance of such changes.

Cookies

This site uses cookies, which are small data files that are generated on your computer, which stores information without providing references to deduce personal information from this data.

You can configure your browser to notify and reject the storage of cookies sent by this site, without this affecting the ability to access the content. However, we are not responsible for the deactivation of these may affect your experience on the web site, like the posibility to share your comments, experiences with other users or be able to post in the forum.

Marks Web / Web Beacons

Like the cookies this site may also contain Web beacons, an electronic image that permits count the number of visitors, users to access the site or accessing certain cookies the same way, thus, we can provide a more personalized experience.

Actions of third parties

Also, you will find within this site, pages, promotions and microsites, surveys, sponsors, advertisers, partners, etc, together with other shared services, which this site may disclose information provided by you under your approval.

The information provided on these sites is subject to the privacy policies or legends of information that are deployed in such sites and is not subject to this privacy policy. We strongly recommend that the Members to review in detail the privacy policies that are deployed on the third party sites.

Privacy Policy Advertising provided at this site:

We studied the preferences of our users, their demographic characteristics, traffic patterns, and other information together to better understand who our audience are and what you need. The tracking of users' preferences also helps us serve you more relevant advertising.

Privacy Policy Tracking Sources Used In This Site:

> 

**Policy on Personal Data Protection**

To use certain services or access certain content, like web comments you must provide certain personal information, which will only be used for the purpose they were collected.

The type of information that he may be requested includes, but not limited to, your name, email address (e-mail), date of birth, sex, occupation, city and country of origin and personal interests, among others, not all information requested at the time to participate in the binding site is obligatory, except that we deem appropriate and so we let you know.

As a general principle, **this site will not share or disclose information except when authorized by you** or in the following cases:

> * When it is required by a competent authority and subject to the fulfillment of legal proceedings and related  
>  * When in the opinion of this site is necessary to enforce the terms of use and other terms of this page, or to safeguard the integrity of other users or the site.

And be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personal information online in a public area like the forum, comments page or chat, that information can be collected and used by others. We do not control the actions of our visitors.

Responsible behavior

All information provided must be true. For these purposes, you guarantee the authenticity of all data that communicates as a result of the completion of the necessary forms for subscription to the Services, access to content or restricted areas of the site. In any case you will be solely responsible for any false or inaccurate conduct and the damages caused to third parties in this site or the information provided.

You agree to act with responsibly at this site and to treat other visitors with respect.

Contact

If you have questions or concerns about this Policy, please do not hesitate to [contact us](mailto:contact@mipony.net) at any time via the contact form available on site or via email  
  
---
